This video introduces the mode and editor-related updates for you.
In the previous CLO version,
when adding a project file, you cannot choose the color scheme you want from the open file.
To change the color scheme, you can only do it in the color editor after opening the file.
From the current version, when adding a project file,
you can choose the color scheme you want to open.
When you want to design a clothing style,
but you also want to add a specific color scheme to the current project,
this function is very useful.
Find the file,
add the project,
open the project file you want,
and in the window that pops out, the color option is added below the clothing.
In the drop-down menu, select the color scheme to be added.
You can choose all or customize it.
Click the color button on the right to select the color scheme.
It is convenient for you to see the color scheme of each color.
The color scheme of each color will be displayed as the most fabric used in the clothing.
Please note that the file created in the 2025.0 or earlier version
will only display the name of the color scheme and not the color scheme.
If you choose all,
the color scheme of the file you have added and the file you have added
will be saved in the order of the project file.
Click the same order to combine.
Therefore, if you want them to match each other,
in both project files,
the color scheme is very important in the same order and preservation.
Please note that if you want to add less color schemes
to the projects that already have more color schemes,
you will use the first color scheme to fill in the remaining color schemes.
As usual,
when you want to customize the color scheme,
find the file, increase the project,
open the project file you want,
click the right button at the bottom of the clothing in the pop-up window,
open the color list to select the color scheme you want to add,
then the file will be combined according to the color scheme selected.
For example, I have now selected the second and third colors of the swimsuit suit.
After adding,
they will be added to the first two color schemes of the current project.
The first color scheme selected by the added project
is the color scheme 2 and black in this case,
which will always be the combat suit,
and will combine with the remaining color schemes in the current project.
In the future, more options will be added
to be able to mix and match the color scheme of different projects.
This update can help users improve the work efficiency of color combination design.
In the latest version of CLO,
we optimized the key frame animation settings.
The main improvements include
the color key frame animation that supports the twist material,
the key frame animation that lights up in the Vray rendering,
and the new time-limited selection layer function.
Open the color editor,
add the key frame to each color animation column,
and add the key frame animation to each color animation column.
Then click the play preview effect.
You can see that the color key frame is applied,
the color of the twist and the color of the twist is changed.
This makes the animation transition more natural.
Open the rendering window,
render lighting settings.
You can see that the light bulb icon has now been removed,
but you can use the fire option to replace it.
After using the fire option, you can also set more content.
Users can add key frames to each of the following settings,
such as intensity, angle, color, width and height, etc.
Here, the light bulb key frame is added to the animation.
Then set the key frame to the following options.
You can control the strength and angle of different stages of lighting in the animation.
This can be used to adjust the light bulb.
In addition, we have also improved the control of the circle size setting.
After starting this setting,
you can also edit the radius,
head shadow height and ground mix settings.
And each setting can be added to the key frame.
Finally, you can adjust the time range of the current animation.
Click on the right on the animation layer.
Select to limit the time range to the selected layer.
You can see that the play area will be adjusted to the selected layer range.
Finally, select to finally render the animation.
You can get the animation of the twist color and light.
I hope these updates can improve your animation experience and simplify your workflow.
In the previous version, the project with GLTF format is not supported by the virtual model animation.
Therefore, any joint animation applied to virtual models or animation based on storage will not be saved.
Thank you for watching.
In the new version, you can now choose to include virtual model animation.
This optimization provides greater flexibility for animation processing.
So you can easily integrate virtual models into various platforms or workflow.
Find the file and select to export GLTF 2.0 GLTF.
In the window, select all virtual models.
In the options below, select virtual model animation.
Select the animation type you want.
When you want to keep the structure of Google to edit or play in the future, this is an ideal choice.
To bind Google's model, the best choice is to implement the high guarantee animation.
You can flexibly choose the export settings that are most suitable for your project needs.
To get better compatibility files.
Whether you are dedicated to interactive experience or high-quality visual display.
This function can make you more free to create and perform virtual model animation.
Thank you for watching.